Inventory of the National Cattlemen’s Association records, 1898-2018
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Subject Files, Series VI.
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Drug Legislation, Related Information and Material II, 1971-1975 (Box 285, Folders 9-10)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-FDA, DES Material and Information II, 1972-1974 (Box 285, Folders 11-12)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-DES Material and Information III, 1975 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-DES Material and Information IV, 1976-1977 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-FDA, DES Material and Information IV, 1976-1977 (Box 286, Folders 3-5)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-FDA, General Correspondence, and Information, 1973-1977 (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-General Drugs-Research, Studies I, 1974-1977 (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-FDA-Organization and Administration, 1965-1976 (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Other Drugs and Chemicals-Regulations and Information, FDA, 1963-1975 (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Listings of New Animal Drugs, 1972-1974 (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Other Drugs, Material, and Information, 1962-1977 (Box 286, Folder 11)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Prosecutions-DES and Other Residues, 1971-1972 (Box 286, Folder 12)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Regulations, Other Drugs, Chemical Additives, 1959-1974 (Box 286, Folders 13-18)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Requests for Certificates-Certification Program, 1972 (Box 286, Folder 19)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Request for Certificates, Certification Program, 1975 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Residue Reports and Detection-Other Drugs and Chemicals, 1973-1977 (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Statutes and Amendments-Food and Drugs, 1962, 1964 (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Suits and Court Cases-DES, 1971 (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Livestock Drugs, Chemicals, and Additives-Withdrawal and Restrictions-DES, 1971-1975 (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Livestock Export Marketing Forum, 1982 (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - Livestock Improvement-Brucellosis Eradication, 1967-1976 (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - Livestock Improvement-Hog Cholera Eradication, 1966-1975 (Box 287, Folder 8)
  - Livestock Improvement-State Brand Laws and Progress, 1971 (Box 287, Folder 9)
  - Livestock Industry Congress, 1985 (Box 287, Folder 10)
  - Livestock Industry Forum, 1962-1963 (Box 287, Folders 11-13)
  - Livestock Industry Institute, 1981-1987 (Box 287, Folder 14)
  - Livestock Industry Promotion Corporation, 1982-1987 (Box 287, Folder 15)
  - Livestock Industry Promotion Corporation-Hattori, Dr. Shinji, 1985 (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Livestock Institute Congress, 1986 (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Livestock Loss Prevention-Brucellosis Eradication, 1967-1977 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Livestock Loss Prevention-Foot and Mouth Disease Eradication, 1967-1975 (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Livestock Loss Prevention-Hog Cholera Eradication Program, 1961-1977 (Box 288, Folders 5-6)
  - Livestock Loss Prevention-Meat Animal Identification Programs, 1964-1976 (Box 288, Folders 7-12)
  - Livestock Loss Prevention-Pseudorabies Eradication, undated (Box 288, Folder 13)
  - Livestock Loss Prevention-Trichinosis Eradication, 1969 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Livestock Losses, 1941 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Livestock Marketing Association, 1980 (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - Livestock Marketing Congress, 1981-1982 (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - Livestock Numbers, 1951-1952 (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Livestock Payment, 1975 (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - Livestock Payment II, 1975 (Box 289, Folders 7-9)
  - Livestock Payment, 1975-1976 (Box 289, Folder 10)
  - Livestock Permitted on National Forests, 1945-1947 (Box 289, Folder 11)
  - Livestock Permitted on National Forests, 1936, 1939-1953 (Box 290, Folders 1-8)
  - Livestock Slaughter by States, 1953-1954 (Box 290, Folder 9)
  - Lobbying, 1977, 1980 (Box 290, Folder 10)
  - Lomasney, William F., 1963-1964 (Box 290, Folder 11)
  - Loomix Incorporated, 1980-1985 (Box 290, Folder 12)
  - Louisiana Beef Promotion Month, 1985-1986 (Box 290, Folder 13)
  - Management Improvement Plan, 1984 (Box 290, Folder 14)
  - Marketing Futures, 1980-1981 (Box 290, Folders 15-17)
  - Marketing Group, 1985-1986 (Box 290, Folder 18)
  - Marketing Research, 1946-1947 (Box 290, Folder 19)
  - Maturity Information on Grading, 1961 (Box 290, Folder 20)
  - Grain-Livestock Controversy, 1970-1977 (Box 290, Folder 21)
  - Meat Board-South Africa, 1988 (Box 290, Folder 22)
  - Meat Consumption Trends, 1962-1963 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Meat Deduction Endorsements, 1954-1958, undated (Box 291, Folders 2-9)
  - Meat Export Federation, 1978-1981 (Box 291, Folders 10-21)
  - Meat Import Act of 1964, 1974-1983 (Box 292, Folders 1-8)
  - Meat Import Act of 1978, 1976-1980 (Box 292, Folders 9-11)
  - Meat Import Act of 1978, 1975-1980 (Box 293, Folders 1-10)
  - Meat Import Act of 1978, 1978, 1981 (Box 294, Folders 1-5)
  - Meat Importers Council of America Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 294, Folder 6)
  - Meat Imports, 1958-1978 (Box 294, Folders 7-15)
  - Meat Imports, 1961-1964, 1977, undated (Box 295, Folders 1-6)
  - Meat Imports and Foreign Trade Statistics - Determinations, 1964-1970 (Box 687, Folders 3-4)
  - Meat Inspection, 1965-1971, 1980 (Box 295, Folders 7-13)
  - Meat Inspection, 1967-1969, 1971-1973, 1980 (Box 296, Folders 1-8)
  - Meat Inspection, 1965-1973, 1980, undated (Box 297, Folders 1-10)
  - Meat Inspection, “Chicken Hot Dogs,”, 1968 (Box 297, Folders 11-12)
  - Meat Inspection, “Chicken Hot Dogs,”, 1968 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Meat Inspection-Domestic, 1983-1984 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Meat Inspection, Enforcement Proceedings, 1969-1973 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Meat Inspection, Legislation, 1962-1967 (Box 298, Folders 4-7)
  - Meat Inspection, Swine Identification, 1970 (Box 298, Folder 8)
  - Meat Inspection, Tuberculosis, 1971 (Box 298, Folder 9)
  - Meat Inspection, Investigations of Violations, 1967, 1970 (Box 298, Folder 10)
  - Meat Inspection Act of 1967-House Bills and Amendments, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 298, Folders 11-14)
  - Meat Inspection Act of 1967-Senate Bills and Amendments, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 298, Folders 15-16)
  - Meat Inspection Act-Violations, Charges, and Indictments, 1966-1976 (Box 298, Folder 17)
  - Meat Inspection Law of 1967 (Box 298, Folder 18)
  - Meat Management, Publications, 1943 (Box 298, Folder 19)
  - Meat Merchandising, 1981 (Box 298, Folder 20)
  - Meat Packing, 1983 (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Meat Promotion, 1955, 1957 (Box 299, Folders 2-3)
  - Meat Promotion-Posters, 1954-1956 (Box 299, Folders 4-9)
  - Meat Promoters, 1977 (Box 299, Folder 10)
  - Meat Sheet, 1974 (Box 299, Folder 11)
  - Mechanically Deboned Meat, 1976-1984 (Box 299, Folders 12-15)
  - Mechanically Deboned Meat, 1976-1984 (Box 300, Folders 1-7)
  - Medical Advisory Council, 1977-1982 (Box 300, Folder 8)
  - Medicated Feed, 1980-1981 (Box 300, Folder 9)
  - Meeting on Issues, 1986 (Box 300, Folder 10)
  - Membership, 1982-1983 (Box 300, Folder 11)
  - Membership, 1980-1984 (Box 301, Folders 1-5)
  - Merchandising/Promotion, 1975 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - Merger with National Livestock Feeders Association, 1974-1977 (Box 301, Folders 7-11)
  - Merger with National Livestock Feeders Association, 1972-1977 (Box 302, Folders 1-9)
  - Mexican Border Fence, 1951 (Box 302, Folder 10)
  - Mexico, 1976-1978 (Box 302, Folder 11)
  - Mexico-U.S. Sanitary Treaty, Publications, 1930-1935 (Box 302, Folder 12)
  - Microcomputers, 1980-1981 (Box 302, Folder 13)
  - Mid America Commodity Exchange, 1982 (Box 302, Folder 14)
  - Mid-America Dairymen, 1986 (Box 302, Folder 15)
  - Midwestern Conference on Food, Agriculture, and Public Policy, 1980 (Box 302, Folder 16)
  - Migratory Labor, Legislation, 1961 (Box 302, Folder 17)
  - Milk Price Support Program, 1982-1983 (Box 302, Folder 18)
  - Millikin, Senator Eugene D., 1956 (Box 302, Folder 19)
  - Minimum Wage, 1965-1968 (Box 303, Folders 1-11)
  - Minimum Wage, 1967 (Box 304, Folders 1-2)
  - Missouri Governor’s Conference, 1985 (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - Mitchell, Albert K., 1956-1964 (Box 304, Folders 4-6)
  - Motor Carrier Act of 1980-Oversight, 1981 (Box 304, Folder 7)
  - Mountain/Plains Meat Club, 1985 (Box 304, Folder 8)
  - Multilateral Trade Negotiations-Agricultural Policy Advisory Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 304, Folder 9)
  - Multilateral Trade Negotiations-Agricultural Policy Advisory Committee II, 1975 (Box 304, Folders 10-13)
  - Nation-Wide Committee on Import-Export Policy, 1960-1964 (Box 305, Folders 1-3)
  - National Advisory Board Council, 1957, 1966-1967, undated (Box 305, Folders 4-8)
  - National Advisory Commission on Food and Fiber, 1965-1967 (Box 305, Folders 9-13)
  - National Advisory Commission on Food and Fiber, 1967 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - The National Agricultural Bankers Conference, 1980 (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - National Agriculture Week, 1988 (Box 306, Folder 3)
  - National Agri-Marketing Association, 1987 (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - National Association of Bar Executives, 1987 (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - National Association of Counties, 1966 (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - National Association County Agricultural Agents, 1987 (Box 306, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Electric Companies, 1963 (Box 306, Folder 8)
  - National Association of Farm Broadcasters, 1967-1987 (Box 306, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Food Chains, 1949-1969 (Box 306, Folders 10-17)
  - National Association of Marketing-Survey of 1959 State Legislation for Marketing Promotional Activities (Box 306, Folder 18)
  - National Association of Marketing Officials, 1958, 1961 (Box 306, Folder 19)
  - National Association of Meat Purveyors, 1986 (Box 306, Folder 20)
  - National Association of Retail Grocers of the United States, 1961-1965 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - National Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts, 1965 (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - National Association of Television and Radio Farm Directors, 1952-1954, 1956 (Box 307, Folders 3-4)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1963 (Box 307, Folder 5)
  - National Association of Television and Radio Farm Directors, 1950s-1963, undated (Box 307, Folders 6-10)
  - National Beef Cook-Off, 1982, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 307, Folders 11-14)
  - National Beef Council, 1951-1961 (Box 307, Folders 15-17)
  - National Beef Council, 1955-1962, undated (Box 308, Folders 1-12)
  - National Beef Council, 1954-1961 (Box 309, Folders 1-9)
  - National Beef Forum, 1981 (Box 309, Folders 10-12)
  - National Beef Grading Conference, 1981 (Box 309, Folder 13)
  - National Beef Profit Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 309, Folders 14-15)
  - National Beef Symposium, 1981-1982 (Box 309, Folder 16)
  - National Brucellosis Technical Commission, 1978 (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - National Cattle Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - National Cholesterol Education, 1986 (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - National Commission on Constitutional Government, 1965 (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - National Commission on Food Marketing, 1964-1966, undated (Box 310, Folders 5-11)
  - National Commission on Food Marketing, 1965-1967 (Box 311, Folders 1-7)
  - National Commission on Water Quality, 1974 (Box 311, Folder 8)
  - National Conference of Commodity Organizations, 1957 (Box 311, Folder 9)
  - National Cowboy Hall of Fame, 1955, 1959-1964 (Box 311, Folders 10-11)
  - National Cowboy Hall of Fame, 1957-1962, undated (Box 312, Folders 1-10)
  - National Energy Plan III (NEPIII), 1981 (Box 312, Folder 11)
  - National Environmental Development Association, 1980 (Box 312, Folder 12)
  - National Farm Institute, 1968 (Box 312, Folder 13)
  - National Farm-City Week, 1955-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 312, Folders 14-16)
  - National Farm-City Week, 1955-1956, 1958-1968 (Box 313, Folders 1-10)
  - National Farm-City Committee, 1956, 1963 (Box 313, Folder 11)
  - National Farm Home Editors, 1960-1963 (Box 313, Folder 12)
  - National Farmers Organization, 1962-1968 (Box 313, Folders 13-14)
  - National Farmers Organization, 1962-1968 (Box 314, Folders 1-5)
  - National Farmers Union, 1953, 1961-1967 (Box 314, Folders 6-8)
  - National Finals Rodeo, 1981, 1985 (Box 314, Folders 9-10)
  - National Food Conference, 1959 (Box 314, Folder 11)
  - National Forests, 1945-1958 (Box 314, Folders 12-18)
  - National Forests-Colorado, 1945-1949, undated (Box 314, Folders 19-22)
  - National Forests-Colorado, 1945-1946 (Box 315, Folders 1-2)
  - National Forests-Multiple Use, 1960 (Box 315, Folders 3-7)
  - National Frozen Food Locker Institute, 1954-1956 (Box 315, Folder 8)
  - National Grange, 1955-1968, undated (Box 315, Folders 9-11)
  - National Grasslands, 1980 (Box 315, Folder 12)
  - National Grazing Lands and People Workshop, 1982 (Box 315, Folder 13)
  - National Hereford Congress, 1956 (Box 315, Folders 14-17)
  - National Heritage Legislation, 1980 (Box 315, Folders 18-23)
  - National Hide Association, 1960-1967, undated (Box 316, Folders 1-7)
  - National Highway Users Conference, Inc., 1958-1963 (Box 316, Folders 8-11)
  - National Highway Users Conference, Inc., 1959-1969 (Box 317, Folders 1-8)
  - National Highway Users Conference, Inc., 1959-1969 (Box 318, Folders 1-8)
  - National Highway Users Conference, Inc., 1960-1966 (Box 319, Folders 1-4)
  - National Historic Preservation Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - National Independent Meat Packers Association, 1955-1968 (Box 319, Folders 6-9)
  - National Institute of Animal Agriculture, 1960-1967 (Box 319, Folders 10-13)
  - National Lamb Feeders, 1960-1968 (Box 319, Folder 14)
  - National Livestock and Meat Board, 1951-1955, 1963-1968 (Box 319, Folders 15-17)
  - National Livestock and Meat Board, 1956-1964 (Box 320, Folders 1-8)
  - National Livestock and Meat Board, 1965-1969, 1981-1988, undated (Box 321, Folders 1-8)
  - National Livestock and Meat Board, 1951-1969, 1983 (Box 322, Folders 1-12)
  - National Livestock and Meat Board, 1951-1968, 1983, undated (Box 323, Folders 1-12)
  - National Livestock and Meat Board, 1982, 1984-1988 (Box 324, Folders 1-6)
  - National Livestock and Meat Board, 1977-1985, 1987-1989 (Box 325, Folders 1-8)
  - National Livestock Auction Association, 1954-1956 (Box 325, Folders 9-12)
  - National Livestock Brand Conference, 1951-1952, 1954-1955 (Box 325, Folders 13-14)
  - National Livestock Brand Conference, 1951-1961, 1967 (Box 326, Folders 1-6)
  - National Livestock Dealers Association, 1963 (Box 326, Folder 7)
  - National Livestock Exchange, 1956 (Box 326, Folder 8)
  - National Livestock Feeders Association, 1960-1977 (Box 326, Folders 9-18)
  - National Livestock Feeders Association-Federal Grading Committee, 1963 (Box 326, Folder 19)
  - National Livestock Feeders Association-Foreign Trade Legislation, 1962-1964 (Box 326, Folders 20-22)
  - National Livestock Feeders Association-Foreign Trade Legislation, 1961-1964 (Box 327, Folders 1-4)
  - National Livestock Feeders Association-Jewel Tea vs. Meat Cutters, 1963-1965 (Box 327, Folders 5-8)
  - National Livestock Feeders Association-Special Committee on Federal Grading, 1963-1964 (Box 327, Folder 9)
  - National Livestock Feeders Association-Special Committee on Federal Grading, 1960, 1962-1964 (Box 328, Folders 1-3)
  - National Livestock Producers Association, 1956-1967, 1981-1986 (Box 328, Folders 4-6)
  - National Livestock Promotion Board, 1956 (Box 328, Folders 7-9)
  - National Livestock Rail Transportation Meeting, 1967-1968 (Box 328, Folders 10-15)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1945-1967 (Box 328, Folders 16-17)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1943-1958, 1968-1969 (Box 329, Folders 1-8)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1959-1963 (Box 330, Folders 1-7)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 331, Folders 1-7)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 332, Folders 1-6)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 333, Folders 1-7)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 334, Folders 1-7)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1969 (Box 335, Folders 1-7)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1944-1969 (Box 336, Folders 1-9)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1944-1977, undated (Box 337, Folders 1-10)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee-Debt, 1977 (Box 337, Folder 11)
  - National Livestock Tax Committee-Debt, 1974-1981 (Box 338, Folders 1-4)
  - National Meat Association, 1980 (Box 338, Folder 5)
  - National Milk Producers Federation, 1983-1987 (Box 338, Folder 6)
  - National Parks, 1959-1980 (Box 338, Folders 7-8)
  - National Press Releases, 1967, 1980 (Box 338, Folder 9)
  - National Parks, 1961, undated (Box 338, Folders 10-11)
  - National Pedigreed Livestock Council, 1988 (Box 338, Folder 12)
  - National Political Conventions-1960 (Box 338, Folder 13)
  - National Political Conventions-1968 (Box 338, Folders 14-17)
  - National Political Conventions-1968 (Box 339, Folders 1-2)
  - National Pork Producers Council, 1983-1984 (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - National Press Photographers Association, 1950s-1963, undated (Box 339, Folders 4-7)
  - National Public Lands Coordinating Committee, 1955, 1962-1964 (Box 339, Folders 8-15)
  - National Restaurant Association, 1956, 1963 (Box 339, Folder 16)
  - National Safety Council, 1963-1966 (Box 339, Folders 17-19)
  - National Western Stock Show, 1981-1986 (Box 340, Folder 1)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1966-1967 (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - National Wool Growers Association, 1956-1969, 1984, undated (Box 340, Folders 3-14)
  - National Wool Growers Association, 1957 (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Nationwide System of Trails, 1965 (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Natural Diversity, 1980 (Box 341, Folder 3)
  - Natural Resources, 1959-1960 (Box 341, Folders 4-5)
  - Navarro City Beef Clinic, 1985 (Box 341, Folder 6)
  - NCA/AMI/FMI Exchange Tour, 1985 (Box 341, Folder 7)
  - NCA/BIC Staff “Supply/Demand” Think Tank, 1983, 1985 (Box 341, Folders 8-12)
  - NCA Building, Alabama Cattlemen’s Association-Calf Donations, 1981 (Box 341, Folder 13)
  - NCA Building, Artists, 1981 (Box 341, Folders 14-15)
  - NCA Building, Audit Procedures, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 16)
  - NCA Building, Bond Issue Application, 1980 (Box 341, Folder 17)
  - NCA Building, Budgets, 1978-1979 (Box 341, Folder 18)
  - NCA Building, Building Plaques, 1982 (Box 341, Folder 19)
  - NCA Building, Campaign Cabinet, Minutes, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 20)
  - NCA Building, Campaign Plan, 1979 (Box 341, Folder 21)
  - NCA Building, Colorado Foundations, 1979, 1981 (Box 342, Folder 1)
  - NCA Building, Fact Sheet, 1980-1982 (Box 342, Folder 2)
  - NCA Building, Financial Statements, 1980-1982 (Box 342, Folder 3)
  - NCA Building, HWH Associates, Inc., 1980 (Box 342, Folder 4)
  - NCA Building, NCA Information, 1979 (Box 342, Folder 5)
  - NCA Building, NCA Regions Map, undated (Box 342, Folder 6)
  - NCA Building, New Mexico Contributors, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 7)
  - NCA Building, Newsletter-Update, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 8)
  - NCA Building-Open House Ceremony, 1982 (Box 342, Folder 9)
  - NCA Building, Presentation-Script, 1979 (Box 342, Folder 10)
  - NCA Building, Printed Material, 1979-1982 (Box 342, Folders 11-13)
  - NCA Building, Prospects-Land for Building, 1980 (Box 342, Folder 14)
  - NCA Building, Questions and Answers, 1979 (Box 342, Folder 15)
  - NCA Building, Recognition, 1979 (Box 342, Folder 16)
  - NCA Building, Rooms-Value Listing (Recognition), 1981 (Box 342, Folder 17)
  - NCA Building, Seed Stock and Western Art Sale and Show, 1980-1981 (Box 342, Folders 18-21)
  - NCA Building, Suggested Prospects, 1979 (Box 342, Folder 22)
  - NCA Building, Tax Deductibility Information, 1976-1979 (Box 342, Folder 23)
  - NCA Building, Texas Contributors, 1980 (Box 343, Folder 1)
  - NCA Building, Utah Contributors, 1981-1982 (Box 343, Folder 2)
  - NCA Building-Building Fund Campaign, 1977-1982 (Box 343, Folders 3-16)
  - NCA Building-Building Fund Campaign, 1978-1982 (Box 344, Folders 1-16)
  - NCA Building-Building Fund Campaign, 1972, 1978-1982 (Box 345, Folders 1-16)
  - NCA History, 1970s, 1982 (Box 346, Folders 1-4)
  - NCA/NLSMB Joint Meeting, 1980 (Box 346, Folder 5)
  - NCA/NLSMB/LMA Meeting, 1986 (Box 346, Folder 6)
  - NCA RCA/RPA Task Force, 1980-1981 (Box 346, Folder 7)
  - NCA Sponsorships, 1985 (Box 346, Folder 8)
  - Net Weight Labeling, 1980 (Box 346, Folder 9)
  - New Farmers and Ranchers, 1981 (Box 346, Folder 10)
  - New World of Agriculture Forum, 1985-1986 (Box 346, Folder 11)
  - New York Times-Residues in Meat, 1983 (Box 346, Folder 12)
  - New Zealand, 1961 (Box 346, Folder 13)
  - New Zealand Meat Producers Board, 1968 (Box 346, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Farm Editors Association, 1960-1962 (Box 346, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Farm Editors of America, 1981, 1985 (Box 346, Folder 16)
  - Ninety Day Price Freeze, 1955 (Box 346, Folders 17-18)
  - Nitrates, 1980 (Box 346, Folder 19)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1972 (Box 346, Folder 20)
  - Officers Trip to Japan, 1987 (Box 346, Folder 21)
  - Officers Trip to Washington D.C., 1981-1982 (Box 346, Folders 22-23)
  - Oficina Permanente de la Carne (International Permanent Meat Office), 1981 (Box 346, Folder 24)
  - Oklahoma State University Days for Families, 1985 (Box 346, Folder 25)
  - Olsen, Claude, 1953-1956 (Box 346, Folders 26-27)
  - O’Mahoney, Joseph C., USS, 1956 (Box 346, Folder 28)
  - O’Neill, Robert, undated (Box 346, Folder 29)
  - Organization for Trade Cooperation, 1957 (Box 346, Folders 30-31)
  - Organized Trade Cooperation, 1956-1957 (Box 346, Folder 32)
  - NCA Building-Building Fund Campaign, 1979-1982 (Box 347, Folders 1-8)
  - NCA Building-National Cattlemen’s Foundation Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 347, Folders 9-10)
  - NCA History, 1934-1985, undated (Box 347, Folders 11-16)
  - Organization for Trade Cooperation, Submittal, 1957 (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Outdoor Recreation, 1963-1969 (Box 348, Folders 2-13)
  - Outdoor Recreation Resources Commission, 1960 (Box 349, Folder 1)
  - Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission, 1960-1963, undated (Box 349, Folders 2-5)
  - Outdoor Recreation Resources Commission, 1960, 1962 (Box 349, Folder 6)
  - Owyhee County Range Tour, 1982 (Box 349, Folder 7)
  - Pacific Legal Foundation, 1984-1986 (Box 349, Folder 8)
  - Packer Feeding, 1967-1980 (Box 349, Folder 9)
  - Packers and Stockyards Act, 1957-1960 (Box 349, Folders 10-12)
  - Packers and Stockyards Act, Amendment, 1957 (Box 349, Folders 13-15)
  - Packers and Stockyards Act, Proposed Amendment-Brand Inspection Section, 1950 (Box 349, Folders 16-17)
  - Packers and Stockyards Act-H.R. 3538, 1958 (Box 349, Folders 18-21)
  - Packers Consent Decree of 1920, 1929-1957 (Box 349, Folders 22-23)
  - Palm Oil, 1976-1977 (Box 349, Folder 24)
  - Parasites, ECTO, 1984 (Box 349, Folder 25)
  - Parity, 1978 (Box 349, Folder 26)
  - Price Fixing, 1978 (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - Price Flexibility, 1980 (Box 350, Folder 2)
  - Price Freezes, 1955 (Box 350, Folders 3-4)
  - Price Spreads, 1955-1958, 1975, 1980 (Box 350, Folders 5-6)
  - Price Supports, 1949-1953 (Box 350, Folders 7-10)
  - Pricing and Reporting, 1976-1981 (Box 350, Folders 11-16)
  - Private Lands-Crop Insurance, 1977-1979 (Box 350, Folder 17)
  - Private Lands-Eminent Domain, 1978 (Box 350, Folder 18)
  - Parliamentary Procedure, undated (Box 351, Folder 1)
  - Party Platforms, 1980 (Box 351, Folder 2)
  - Past Presidents, 1980 (Box 351, Folder 3)
  - Payment in Kind Program (PIK), 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folders 4-7)
  - Payment in Lieu of Taxes, 1980 (Box 351, Folder 8)
  - PCB, 1979-1984 (Box 351, Folder 9)